<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Sri RangaNadh Kakarla on Home</title>
    <link>https://ranga6897.github.io/web/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Sri RangaNadh Kakarla on Home</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 Aug 2020 11:14:48 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://ranga6897.github.io/web/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Effect of COVID-19.</title>
      <link>https://ranga6897.github.io/web/post/project-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Aug 2020 11:14:48 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ranga6897.github.io/web/post/project-4/</guid>
      <description>This work is a part of a Group Project.
The Idea for this project was given by Miss.Meghana (meghana952@gmail.com).
My Contribution in the Project :
 Imputing Null Values using Decision tree classifier and Gradient boost classifier. Performed Uni-Variate, Bi-Variate and Multi-Variate Analysis. Performed Statistical tests to compare the relation between past and present data. Built different machine learning models assuming target variable as spending kind and tried to explain the outcome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Text Extractor</title>
      <link>https://ranga6897.github.io/web/post/project-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jun 2020 11:13:32 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ranga6897.github.io/web/post/project-3/</guid>
      <description>Idea : Tool that collects our Health parameters and store them. Success : No
Work I Did :
 Extracting Images From a pdf file. Pre-Processing the Image using OpenCV library. Extraction of text from the Image using Pytesseract tool. Getting Values using key words and RegEx functions.  Work I Think I Should do :
 Use NLTK for getting desired text. Able to Identify the change in the parameters.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rice Price Estimator</title>
      <link>https://ranga6897.github.io/web/post/project-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 May 2020 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ranga6897.github.io/web/post/project-1/</guid>
      <description>The DataSet used is the project is RiceFarms Dataset.Description Performed Uni-Variate Analysis and Bi-variate Analysis wrt to price,region. Engineered Features that gives insights about the land such as gross_output_per_square_meter, spending_per_square_meter. Performed Statistical test such as Anova, Chi-Square Test of Independence. Built two separate models to predict the Region and to predict the price of rice.  GitHub link</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Web Data Extraction</title>
      <link>https://ranga6897.github.io/web/post/project-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 May 2020 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ranga6897.github.io/web/post/project-2/</guid>
      <description>Why : I Built for someone else. Success : Yes.
 Different SKUs(Stock Keeping Unit) are loaded from DataBase and updates the prices in the DataBase. Built using basic tools such as BeautifulSoup and RegEx. This Was my first scrapping project, I learned and built in one day(basic).  GitHub link</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://ranga6897.github.io/web/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ranga6897.github.io/web/contact/</guid>
      <description>You Can Find me on these Platforms.
   Platform URL     Gmail : ksriranganadh6@gmail.com   LinkedIn : https://www.linkedin.com/in/ranganadh6/   GitHub : https://www.github.com/ranga6897   Medium : https://medium.com/@ksriranganadh6    </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>